The Intersection Where Family, Honor and Betrayal Collide.
10th & Wolf is a action, crime, drama film directed by Bobby Moresco.
A former street thug returns to his Philadelphia
home after a stint in the military.
Back on his home turf, he once again finds himself tangling with the mob
boss who was instrumental in his going off to be a soldier.
Tommy, played by James Marsden.
Joey, played by Giovanni Ribisi.
Vincent, played by Brad Renfro.
Brandy, played by Piper Perabo.
Matty Matello, played by Dennis Hopper.
Agent Horvath, played by Brian Dennehy.
10th & Wolf is a 2006 film about the Philadelphia
crime family, directed by Robert Moresco.
It is based on an actual mob war in South Philadelphia.
The movie stars James Marsden, Giovanni Ribisi and Brad Renfro, and features appearances by Dennis Hopper,
Val Kilmer, Piper Perabo, Lesley Ann Warren, Tommy Lee, Francesco Salvi and Brian Dennehy.
10th & Wolf was the last film starring Renfro to be
released before his death at the age of 25.
The film explores themes of philadelphia, pennsylvania,
undercover, mobster, mafia, crime family.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.